Rathal saw at once that the Unsullied Flame was a gift from the Great Soul.
He resolved to harness its power with technology and created Amaterasu.
By the light of Amaterasu's sacred flame, the people began to rebuild.
With its power, they established a new state in the Far East.
The Far East
Stop it! That might seem worthless to you, but to Vulcan it's a precious memory that he shared with his family!
Please! Just leave him alone!
Heard a commotion over the wire I planted on Iris, so I thought I'd come by.
Howie!
Thanks a bunch, now get me out of this thing!
I was planning to relax a moment.
I can't! Everyone at the workshop is in danger right now!
Though I could always just take you home as you are.
I regret my choice already.
Another one?
Arthur! What's happening?
Giovanni's in the workshop! Go take him out!
Go take him out!
I should have guessed. You would hide it in some piece of junk. With this secured, all that's left is to dispose of you.
That's why I'm called Smash the Doctor's creepy-nosent man! Get away from my company's new engineer!
Here's the special
Okay, hit here.
Please.
Take what you got and leave now
You're wearing out your welcome
No one here wants to see you here, yeah
Think that you won from day one
Once the devil will come
You know just why he wants you, don't you?
Your crooked desire
It doesn't feel so right
Misguided, defighted
It's a part of the reason
You're starting a fire
You're gonna watch it burn
Try to save yourself like you always do
Every bridge we build
You think it's just a burning death
Just burn it down
When everything is gone
You'll wish you only hurt us out
Hurt us out
Screaming
Meiji
Shinra, you're here
You're with them?
But why?
You okay, Vulcan?
Can you move?
Feel like I'm gonna need a minute
Took a beating and a blast to the chest
Shinra Kusakabe
Shinra, how'd you escape your restraints?
No matter
I can capture you again once I've dealt with these pests
Thought you guys weren't supposed to let anyone in there
Damn it, so annoying
My shimmers?
I'm sure they are
Since unlike your comrade
You compulsively parry every attack that's thrown at you
You've fallen for my every fate
Warm air becomes light and rises
Whilst cold air does the opposite
You make your illusions by manipulating differences in air density
So if I supply enough heat to make those minute differences irrelevant
Your shimmers fade away
You have no chance
Now, let's end this
Take it easy, I'm on your side
All gravel's the same to me
Except for Shinra
Rise, fishing fire
Wrap him up and hold him in place
What is this?
My flames are magnetically charged
They sense the magnetic fields around living things
And latch onto them
They caught him
Sister, hit the buttons on that wall
You're doing great, sister
Just keep it up, okay?
Latam
Everything you've created is pointless
Latam, Latam, Latam, Latam, Latam, Latam, Latam
Latam
If this keeps up, I'll pass out
I think I'll melt this gravel into asphalt
Wait a sec
Was the sister at it again?
Those machines may be tiny
But each has its own magnetic field
I figured if we release enough of them
We could disrupt the magnetic homing system
Your flames use to target humans
And it looks like I was right
He has the edge in close quarters
I can't maneuver as well in all this gear
Your report led me to believe
That the enemy had been subdued here
Again?
Tell me
Are you the person I just linked with?
That's gotta be you, right?
Your show
Hey, listen
I think that we might be brothers
To be honest
I'm pretty sure of it
I'm Shinra
Your big brother
It's so good to see you
It's your belief that we share blood?
Oh, you're crazy adorable, too
I guess good looks must run in the family
You're gonna be a hit at school, bro
You look like a freaking angel
I can finally make good on my promise now, Mom
I'm gonna protect you
No matter what happens next
I'll always be in your corner, Kay
I see now
The evangelist said I'd know him on sight
And so I do
This is my brother
It's true
This feeling is hard to describe
The only word that comes to mind is disgust
When did he...
As a wielder of the Adola Burst
You need to come with us now
Shinra!
Quite impressive
If he actually reacted
Arthur!
How is he able to move like that?
Why can't I see what he's doing?
I don't get it
Bring the one with the Adola Burst back with us
The rest should be disposed of
Yes, sir
Did you find it?
The key to a Matarasu is ours now
Shinra!
Get in!
Still in one piece, I see
When did you get here?
It's okay
Come on!
Whoa there, Skippy
How'd you get there so quick?
Nice try
The wielder of the Adola Burst
Won't escape my grasp
Sorry, Squirt
But I can't let you have him yet
The heroes arrived
Listen!
I'll come back for you, Sho
I promise!
So you're the man known as Joker
Yeah
Seems my reputation precedes me
That's enough to make even me nervous
Stop interfering in our affairs
I don't intend to let you
Or the Fire Force
Go around doing as you please
Think they've gained enough distance
So there's no point in staying here
He doesn't even have an Adola Link
What a monster
Hey, Captain Obie
Yes, sir
We got the kid to the hospital
Yeah, him and Arthur
The workshop's in shambles
It was definitely the Whiteclad
And Dr. Giovanni?
He's one of them
I also met a kid who I think is my brother
Vulcan's all right
That said
The Whiteclad might come after him again
We'll stay close just in case
Yeah, I think that might be for the best, sir
We'll wait for you to get here
So, uh, Vulcan
Why don't you come to the 8th?
Just as a guest
Think you'd be safer there
Okay
I'll do that
Thanks, Shinra
This isn't how I wanted things to pan out at all
Thought we'd charm you
Convince you that the 8th was the place to be
I'm so sorry
We all fought as hard as we could
But we couldn't protect you
Or your family
You don't have anything to apologize for
You warned me that danger was heading my way
And I made the choice not to listen
I know Ye's just a kid
But he's a lot tougher than he looks
And Lisa isn't really...
There ain't a thing in this world that can't be fixed
So Lisa's gonna come around
And Ye's gonna heal up
Once I've got them
It's back to fixing this world
What about you?
Seeing your brother like that must have hurt
You don't need to worry about me
I know I'm not the only person who's got it bad
It's the world we live in
Same boat and all that
That's true
We're in this together
So, hey
When you start working towards your dream
I'll be glad to help out
Count on it
I appreciate that
Tell me
How did you know to show up just in time to save the day?
Got lucky?
They took so long to get back
I figured I'd go and check on them
Or maybe it's because you were the one who led the white clad out there in the first place
That's ridiculous!
So not true
Why would I bring them there just to help you guys get away from them?
Step one toe out of line and I will crush you until you turn from gravel to sand
Arthur's wounds weren't nearly as bad as I thought
But there's always next time
It wasn't long before Ye was out of the woods as well
At Captain Obi's invitation
Vulcan ended up taking refuge at Company 8
Show really is serving the evangelist
But I'll help him come around
No matter what it takes
I will keep my promise
I'm so sorry about them!
Thought I'd open with that in case our rookies were disrespectful towards you
You're astoundingly stupid
You're polite
Way polite
Their manners were just fine
If anyone was rude, it was me
Food's on the table
Come and get it!
Who made it?
Was it you?
No
The lieutenant cooked it himself
Since we had a guest coming
Whoa, for real?
Hell yeah!
Hey, what's that supposed to mean?
I feel like you can guess
What are you scared to say it yourself?
Wow, this looks amazing
Nice work
I'm friggin' starving
Hey, what's the big idea?
That was punishment for making me defend the workshop by myself
You're kidding me
I was kind of busy getting ambushed, okay?
Well, don't let that happen
Don't act like everything went perfect on your end
Huh?
Sorry, those two can get pretty loud
I grew up in a machine shop
Noise is something I'm used to
Would you two idiots lock it down?
Play nice for our guest
Huh?
Keep your distance
I've plundered enough
And that's good
When the lieutenant's on dinner duty
You know you're in for a treat
I can never stop myself from overeating
It's awful
He's showing us all up
And it guards those recipes like a stingy old granny
Did you get enough?
We've got plenty left over still
Is it always like this here?
Pretty much
Well, Tamaki's Lucky Lutcher lure isn't acting up at the moment
So I guess it's a little bit better than usual
Her lucky what lure?
You know, this really isn't what I was expecting
Listen, Vulcan
Shinra might have told you this already
But our mission at the 8th is to save this planet and the people on it
I know your family never cared for the Fire Force
And I understand why
But there's a place for you here if you want it
That's a standing offer
And even if you decide to decline it
We'll still keep you and yours safe
We only want you to take this job if it's what you want
Why'd Vulcan want to come back to the workshop?
He said he needed to settle some things
Might be picking up stuff too
It would be pretty awesome if he did decide to become our engineer
It really would
Pop, Grandad
Here's your usual sodas
Don't know if you can see me from where you are
But the Fire Force is taking me in
I'm not proud of it
I know they're all tied to Heijima
So, am I disowned?
We swore as a family we'd never help them
But so far it's them that helped me
Maybe our family was cursed for building a Matsurasu
It seems like anything and everything that's precious to me gets broken
Somehow, someway
I have to build something that's too strong to break
I have to fix this world
So life can thrive in it
I thought I could do it all on my own
But then I met Lisa
And Ye
And now this guy from the Fire Force
Who says he wants to help
I'm sorry
Grandad
And Pop
Gave my word
But I'm breaking it
Christina
Church
Chang is different
Daddy
Come on
We are not
We areender
You
How are you now?
Are you
How are you
Heaven is
We have
Back to you
Our
Kah
Green
Won-
Thank you
God
Amen
We are
Thank you
Nam
Everybody
attract
You
Mỹ
I'll see you next time.
And I work best in a place that has style.
Ooh, that doesn't look half bad.
We're not really going to leave that up there, are we?
Company 8 is a ragtag band of misfits even now, so this kind of thing suits us.
Plus, it's totally rock and roll.
Come on, devil, flash your hordes.
Let's rock.
Please stop calling me a devil, sir.
I'm a hero.
Yeah, but devils are a lot more rockin'.
Latum.
You know, I'm a hero.
So you're great.
You